http://www.anderol.com/privacy-statement

CompanyProducts & solutionsInvestorsMediaResponsibilityCareer
LOGIN
HomeProductsFood gradeIndustrialRequest MSDSDistributorsAnderolAnderolKey benefitsAbout syntheticsHistoryLanxessCertificates & approvalsArticlesContact us
HomeProductsFood gradeIndustrialRequest MSDSDistributorsAnderolAnderolKey benefitsAbout syntheticsHistoryLanxessCertificates & approvalsArticlesContact us
Search
Privacy statement
We are aware that the security of your private information from the use of our website is an important concern. We take the protection of your personal data very seriously. Therefore we would like you to know what data we maintain and what data we discard. With this privacy statement, we would like to inform you about our privacy measures.
Collection of Data
You are not required to provide personal information as a condition of using our site, except as may be necessary to provide you a product or service at your request. When you use our website, we store data for various administrative purposes. This data may include the name of your Internet service provider, the website that you used to link to our site, the websites that you visit from our site and your IP-Address. This data could possibly lead to your identification, but we do not use it to do so. We do use the data from time to time for statistical purposes, but maintain the anonymity of each individual user so that the person cannot be identified. In cases when personal data is provided to others to provide you products or services you have requested, or for other purposes you have authorized, we rely on technical and organizational means to assure that applicable data privacy regulations are followed.
Collection and processing of personal data
We collect personal data only when you provide it to us, through registration, completion of forms or e-mails, as part of an order for products or services, inquiries or requests about materials being ordered and similar situations in which you have chosen to provide the information to us.
The database and its contents remain at our company or stay with third parties acting on our behalf and responsible to us. Except as otherwise described in the “Purposes of Use” section below, your personal data will not be passed on by us or by those acting on our behalf for use by third parties in any form whatsoever, unless we have obtained your consent or are legally required to do so.
Some of this data may be stored or processed at computers located in jurisdictions other than the jurisdiction in which you live and whose data protection laws may differ.
Purposes of Use
The data we collect will be used for the purpose of supplying you with the requested products or services and as may otherwise be permitted by law. On certain websites, where you submit personal data, you may be asked to indicate your preferences as to whether or not you wish to receive information and/or promotional materials about our company and its products or services or about third parties with whom we have strategic business relationships and their products and services. We will respect any such preferences as indicated and you will have the ability to change such preference according to the "Right of Cancellation" section below.
Right of Access and Correction
You have the right to review and amend any personal data stored in our system if you believe it may be out of date or incorrect. Just send an e-mail to the address given in the Imprint for this website.
Right of Cancellation
You have the right at any time to withdraw your consent to the use of your personal data in the future, including for purposes of your receiving from our company information and/or promotional materials. Again, just send an e-mail to the address given in the Imprint for this website.
Use of Cookies
In some websites, so-called Cookies are used in order for us to improve the efficiency of your individual use of the website. Cookies are identifiers that our web-server could send to your computer in order to identify the computer being used for the duration of the session. Most browsers are set up to accept these Cookies automatically. In addition, you can deactivate the storing of cookies or adjust your browser to inform you before the Cookie is stored on your computer.
Security
Where indicated, we use the Secure Socket Layer protocol (SSL protocol for short) to help ensure the secure transmission of your details to the server by encrypting customers’ details transmitted on the Internet.
Children
We recognize the importance of protecting children’s privacy. Without the prior, verifiable consent of the legal representative of a child that we know to be under the age of 13, information obtained online from individuals we know to be under 13 years old will only be used by us to respond directly to the child's request and to seek the consent of such child's legal representative, and will not be used for other purposes. Such legal representative has the right, upon request, to view the information provided by the child and/or to require that it be deleted. Any personally identifiable information about the child will be deleted if consent from the child's legal representative is not obtained.
Contacts
Please use the contact information identified in the Imprint for this website with any problems, questions or suggestions that you may have. The constant development of the Internet requires occasional adjustments to our privacy statement. We retain the right to make changes when necessary.
SPECIALTY LUBRICANTS
Follow us
Search (2)FacebookLinkedInYoutubeTwitter
Quick links
Contact usAbout usCertificates & approvalsDistributorsLANXESS
Anderol BVTerms and conditionsPrivacy statement
